<TECHTERMS>
        
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Asynchronous</TITLE>
                <MEANING>Asynchronous programming is a technique that enables your program to start a 
                potentially long-running task and still be able to be responsive to other events while that 
                task runs, rather than having to wait until that task has finished. Once that task has finished, 
                your program is presented with the result.
                </MEANING>
            </WORD>
        

    
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Boolean</TITLE>
                <MEANING>In computer programming, a boolean value is one that can either be TRUE or FALSE. 
                If you need to know “yes” or “no” about something, then you would want to use the 
                boolean function. It sounds extremely simple, but booleans are used all the time in 
                programming, and they are extremely useful.
                </MEANING>
            </WORD>
        

         
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Concatenate</TITLE>
                <MEANING>It is often necessary to join text strings together in a program to make a new text string. 
                This is called concatenation.
                </MEANING>
            </WORD>
    

        
        
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Declaration</TITLE>
                <MEANING> In computer programming, a declaration determines the name and data type of a variable or other element. 
                Programmers declare variables by writing the name of the variable into code, along with any data type indicators 
                and other required syntax.
                </MEANING>
            </WORD>
        

        
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Execution</TITLE>
                <MEANING>Execution in computer and software engineering is the process by which a computer or virtual 
                machine reads and acts on the instructions of a computer program. Each instruction of a program is a 
                description of a particular action which must be carried out, in order for a specific problem to be solved.
                </MEANING>
            </WORD>
        

          
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Function</TITLE>
                <MEANING>A function is simply a “block" of code that you can use over and over again, rather than writing 
                it out multiple times. Functions enable programmers to break down or decompose a problem into smaller chunks, 
                each of which performs a particular task.
                </MEANING>
            </WORD>
        


          <G>
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Graphics</TITLE>
                <MEANING>Typically, the term computer graphics refers to several different things: the representation and 
                manipulation of image data by a computer. the various technologies used to create and manipulate images. 
                </MEANING>
            </WORD>
          </G>

          <H>
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Hoisting</TITLE>
                <MEANING>JavaScript Hoisting refers to the process whereby the interpreter appears to move the declaration of 
                functions, variables or classes to the top of their scope, prior to execution of the code.
                </MEANING>
            </WORD>
          </H>

          <I>
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Interpreted</TITLE>
                <MEANING>In an interpreted language, the source code is not directly translated by the target machine. Instead, 
                a different program, aka the interpreter, reads and executes the code.
                </MEANING>
            </WORD>
        </I>

          <J>
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>JSON</TITLE>
                <MEANING>It is a text-based way of representing JavaScript object literals, arrays, and scalar data. 
                JSON is relatively easy to read and write, while also easy for software to parse and generate. 
                It is often used for serializing structured data and exchanging it over a network, typically between 
                a server and web applications.
                </MEANING>
            </WORD>
        </J>


          <K>
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Key</TITLE>
                <MEANING>
                A key is a piece of information required to retrieve some data.
                </MEANING>
            </WORD>
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Keyword</TITLE>
                <MEANING>Keywords are predefined, reserved words used in programming that have special meanings to the compiler. 
                Keywords are part of the syntax and they cannot be used as an identifier. 
                </MEANING>
            </WORD>
          </K>

          <L>
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Literals</TITLE>
                <MEANING>Constant values that are typed in the program as a part of the source code are called literals. 
                Literals can be of any of the basic data types and can be divided into Integer Numerals, Floating-Point Numerals, 
                Characters, Strings, and Boolean Values.</MEANING>
            </WORD>
        </L>


          <M>
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Memory</TITLE>
                <MEANING>Memory refers to the location of short-term data, while storage refers to the location of data 
                stored on a long-term basis. Memory is most often referred to as the primary storage on a computer, such 
                as RAM. Memory is also where information is processed. It enables users to access data that is stored for 
                a short time.</MEANING>
            </WORD>
        </M>


          <N>
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Nesting</TITLE>
                <MEANING>Nesting occurs when one programming construct is included within another. Nesting allows for powerful, 
                yet simple programming. It reduces the amount of code needed, while making it simple for a programmer to 
                debug and edit. Different types of construct can be nested within another.
                </MEANING>
            </WORD>
        </N>

          <O>
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Object Literal</TITLE>
                <MEANING>An object literal is a list of zero or more pairs of property names and associated values of an object, 
                enclosed in curly braces ( {} ).
                </MEANING>
            </WORD>
        </O>
<!--
          <P>
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Empire Burlesque</TITLE>
                <MEANING>Bob Dylan</ARTIST>
            </WORD>
        </P>

          <Q>
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Empire Burlesque</TITLE>
                <MEANING>Bob Dylan</ARTIST>
            </WORD>
        </Q>

          <R>
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Empire Burlesque</TITLE>
                <MEANING>Bob Dylan</ARTIST>
            </WORD>
        </R>

          <S>
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Empire Burlesque</TITLE>
                <MEANING>Bob Dylan</ARTIST>
            </WORD>
        </S>

          <T>
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Empire Burlesque</TITLE>
                <MEANING>Bob Dylan</ARTIST>
            </WORD>
        </T>

          <U>
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Empire Burlesque</TITLE>
                <MEANING>Bob Dylan</ARTIST>
            </WORD>
        </U>

          <V>
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Empire Burlesque</TITLE>
                <MEANING>Bob Dylan</ARTIST>
            </WORD>
        </V>

          <W>
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Empire Burlesque</TITLE>
                <MEANING>Bob Dylan</ARTIST>
            </WORD>
        </W>

          <X>
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Empire Burlesque</TITLE>
                <MEANING>Bob Dylan</ARTIST>
            </WORD>
        </X>

          <Y>
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Empire Burlesque</TITLE>
                <MEANING>Bob Dylan</ARTIST>
            </WORD>
        </Y>

          <Z>
            <WORD>
                <TITLE>Empire Burlesque</TITLE>
                <MEANING>Bob Dylan</ARTIST>
            </WORD>
        </Z> -->  
</TECHTERMS>
